question_data = [
             {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
              "question": "The Spitfire originated from a racing plane.",
              "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
             {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
              "question": "The book 1984 was published in 1949.", "correct_answer": "True",
              "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
             {"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
              "question": "Vincent van Gogh cut off one of his ears.", "correct_answer": "True",
              "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
             {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
              "question": "Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.",
              "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
             {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
              "question": "The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
              "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
             {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
              "question": "Toronto is the capital city of the North American country of Canada.",
              "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
             {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean",
              "difficulty": "hard",
              "question": "Throughout the entirety of &quot;Dragon Ball Z&quot;, Goku only kills two characters: a miniboss named Yakon and Kid Buu.",
              "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
             {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
              "difficulty": "medium",
              "question": "In career mode of &quot;Need for Speed: Underground 2&quot;, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.",
              "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
             {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
              "question": "Not including false teeth; A human has two sets of teeth in their lifetime.",
              "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
             {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean",
              "difficulty": "medium",
              "question": "Snagglepuss was part of the Yogi Yahooies in the 1977 show Scooby&#039;s All-Star Laff-a-Lympics.",
              "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
 ]


